anyvan.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy | AnyVan

#### Overview

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and subdomains of www.AnyVan.com (the "Site"). By visiting this website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use or access our site.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the AnyVan User Agreement.

#### Information Collection & Use

In order to use this Site, you must first complete the registration/sign up form. During the registration process, you are required to give contact information such as name, address, phone number and email address. This allows us to provide services and features that meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your on-site experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

If you choose to use our Site, we may require you to provide contact and identity information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which are optional with the use of the * symbol. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or individual feature.

We may track certain information based upon your behaviour on the Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interest, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve you and the marketplace. This information may include information such as the URL that you came from, which URL you go to next, your computer browser information, and your IP address.

If you choose to list deliveries, or bid on deliveries on the Site, we collect information about your activity and behaviour. We also collect other users' comments about you in our feedback area.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, phone calls or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

If you email a delivery listing to a friends, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. These details will not be stored and will only be used to send the one-time email.

#### Uses of Your Information

We use your personal information, including your email address, to help facilitate our services to you. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we products and services; inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our User Agreement; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. We may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User IDs. We may also compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

You agree that we may use personal information, including your email address to help our marketing and promotional efforts. Your account information may also be shared with trusted third parties and affiliates. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

#### COMPANY DETAILS

AnyVan LTD - Trading as AnyVan is a company registered in England and Wales and having its registered address at:

The Triangle,  
5-17 Hammersmith Grove,  
Hammersmith,  
London,  
W6 0LG

Registered under the Data Protection Act.

You can contact AnyVan on:

Phone: 020 3005 6000  
E-mail: [info@anyvan.com](mailto:info@anyvan.com)

To unsubscribe from our mailing list simply click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every marketing email and you will be opted out of all email communications.

This company is a member of the **AnyVan Association of Professional Removers**

Find out more

This company is a member of the **AnyVan Association of Professional Car Transporters**

Find out more

This company is a member of the **AnyVan Association of Professional Motorcycle Transporters**

Find out more

Repeat user who has posted a listing on AnyVan previously  
**19% greater chance of quote acceptance!**

**This is a mobile site user.** They are more likely to be in a hurry - a realistic first bid may secure the job!

Repeat user who has accepted a quote on AnyVan previously  
**60% greater chance of quote acceptance!**

This transport provider is currently available today! We highly recommend sending them a message to see if they can undertake your job if it’s urgent.
